<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="40" uniqueCount="37"><si><t>WE-CAN Planning Meeting Tentative Agenda</t></si><si><r><rPr><b/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>Meeting Logistics</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>:</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><b/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>When</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>: Tuesday April 3, 2018, 9AM - 5PM MT</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><b/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>Where</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>: CIRA Directors Conference Room, CSU Foothills Campus</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><b/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>Directions to CSU Foothills Campus</t></r><r><rPr><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t>: https://www.atmos.colostate.edu/department/contact-us/</t></r></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Remote Access:You can join the meeting from your computer, tablet or smartphone. 
https://global.gotomeeting.com/join/685295741 
You can also dial in using your phone. 
United States: +1 (872) 240-3311 
Access Code: 685-295-741 
First GoToMeeting? Do a quick system check: https://link.gotomeeting.com/system-check </t></si><si><t>Start</t></si><si><t>End</t></si><si><t>Agenda Item</t></si><si><t>Discussion Leader</t></si><si><t>Notes</t></si><si><t>Discussion Notes</t></si><si><t>Welcome</t></si><si><t>Emily</t></si><si><t>I'll provide an overview of the key science questions, and the topics we need to discuss today.</t></si><si><t>Introductions</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Everyone </t></si><si><t>Emily will facilitate, but I need each person (or team) to provide one slide that provides a brief description of your role (i.e instrument or forecasting, or logistics) AND photos of everyone from your group. Please do this by March 30.</t></si><si><t>Site Logistics</t></si><si><t>Pavel or Cory</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Overview of Boise Facility, Ops Center, Hangar, Table Space, lack of Fume Hoods, location of aircraft, shipping logistics, etc . Could you provide pictures of the facility in Boise ahead of time so people can think about questions they may have? </t></si><si><t>Break</t></si><si><t>Field Catalog</t></si><si><t>Greg Stossmeister and Scot Loehrer</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Greg will provide an overview of the Field Catalog and Scot Loehrer will discuss Data Management support that EOL can provide. They will likely be remote presentations. Here is a link to the catalog we used during our test flights: http://catalog.eol.ucar.edu/we-can_2017. Please note that all instruments will need to provide preliminary data after each flight, and document whether their instrument performed well during that flight. Please help Greg and I make sure we have a good instrument status reporting set-up to make this easy for you! </t></si><si><t>Mock Forecast</t></si><si><t>Russ/Ravan</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Overview of key forecast products, mock presentation of information. This should be detailed enough so that everyone can provide feedback, and we can identify any missing/anticipated information. </t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Lunch </t></si><si><t>The Foothills Campus is a food desert. I suspect we will have a semi-working lunch finishing any conversations that went too long in the morning.Thus we will order lunch for everyone. Please go to this link: https://catering.panerabread.com/#!/menu/category/111 and click on the “Boxed Lunches” option.  Note that if you scroll down, there is a half salad/half sandwich option. Please input your lunch order on the final tab of this sheet labeled &quot;Lunch order&quot; by COB Thursday March 29th.</t></si><si><t>Anticipated Schedules</t></si><si><t>This will be an overview of our anticipated daily schedule, i.e. when do we need to have our forecast briefings and how far in advance we need to file flight plans. I would also like to reivew individual schedules, particularly with PIs, to understand who will be in Boise when. Please fill in what you know in the Individual Schedules tab. Please also answer as many questions as you can under the Questions for Instrument Teams tab.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Jack - Regarding schedules, one thing that you need to clarify with RAF is who from the plane actually files flight plans with ATC/FAA and what is the lead time required. This could be a problem regarding back to back flights if the only people authorized to do this are the aircrew, and the deadline falls during the first day’s flight. Work around could be having an extra RAF “authorized person&quot; in Boise who could work with your team during flight #1 to plan and file for flight #2. </t></si><si><t>Decision Making</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Overview of factors to consider during daily target choice and flight planning. Emily will provide materials as a starting point for review ahead of time. </t></si><si><t>Wrap Up/Other Concerns/Next Steps</t></si><si><t>If we have time, here are other topics to discuss, please add more: 1) How best to coordinate with BB-Flux, 2) Instrument priorities for Educational Deployment</t></si></sst>